Envi Bagus

UI/UX & Product Designer

A Skilled Product Designer who love making Intuitive user-centered digital products. Have experience working with teams to analyze and create beautiful UI/UX Design based on requirements and design thinking process using atomic design approach.

Email envibagus@gmail.com Phone (+62) 878 6222 0311 Portfolio s.id/NV_Portfolio Linkedin linkedin.com/in/envibagus Location Bali, Indonesia

Experience



SELF EMPLOYED • Jan 2023 - Sep 2023

Freelance UI/UX Designer

- > Designed 5+ Freelance projects of Apps & Websites design.
- [>] Graduated in University (B.I.T. / S.Kom).
- > Expanded knowledge in UI/UX to enhance my problem solving skills, sharpened product design skills.



AIRDROP TECHNOLOGIES • Sep 2022 - Jan 2023

UI/UX Designer

Full-time semi remote - Singapore

- [>] Built company design system for multiple products.
- > Designed and Collaborated with teams in 3 projects correlated in WEB3.
- > Conducted UX Research in multiple projects.
- [>] Directed design team to maximize workflows.



NATIVE PRODUCTIONS · Apr 2022 - June 2023

Freelance UI/UX Designer

Part-time - Bali, Indonesia

- Designed multiple WEB2/WEB3 projects.
- > Conducted UX research and interview before starting projects.
- Coded landing page website projects



IDOOH INDONESIA • May 2022 - Oct 2022

UI/UX Designer

Full-time remote - Jakarta, Indonesia

- Designed and Prototyped 3 products in Tailwind UI styles.
- > Led Design team.
- > Created design system for each products and company.
- > Conducted design thinking for every projects.



TIGA TOKEN DIGITAL • May 2021 - May 2022

UI/UX Designer

Full-time - Bali, Indonesia

- > Designed 6+ projects related to WEB3 including NFT Marketplace, Crypto Wallet Extension, Crypto Exchange, Staking, Crypto Launchpad.
- > Managed end-to-end design process as Solo Designer.
- > Coded landing pages for every products.
- [>] Created graphic design for various events and social media purposes.



VENTRAPEDIA · Dec 2019- Dec 2020

Freelance Web Designer

Part-time - Bali, Indonesia

- [>] Designed Travel agent & community app using Adobe XD.
- > Designed dashboard for travel management platform.
- > Coded all designs using Front-end Frameworks.



Product Designer

Full-time - Bali, Indonesia

- [>] Designed and Managed versioning of Travel agent website app in Figma.
- Managed website using Docker and Linux.
- > Created video motion graphics using Adobe Premiere & After Effects.

(Skills

> Design Thinking

> UX Research

> VIsual Design

> Interaction Design

> Design System > Design Token

> Prototyping > UX Writing

> Figma

> Maze

> Framer

> Notion

> Sketch

> Atlassian

> Adobe Illustrator

> Adobe Photoshop

> HTML & CSS

> SQL Database

> Tailwind

> Bootstrap

> Problem Solving

> Proj. Management

> Leadership

> Attention to detail

> Collaboration

Education

> ITB Stikom Bali (B.IT) Information System. GPA: 3.48 Sep 2019 - Jun 2023

> Harisenin.com Bootcamp Product Manager & UI/UX.

Aug 2022 - Jan 2023

SMK TI Bali Global Vocational High school in Software Eng. Jul 2016 - Jul 2019

😭 Cert. & Awards

- Output
 UX Design for Product Development Skill Academy • Mar 2021
- 3rd Winner of Paras ICT Web design Competition

INSTIKI Indonesia • Feb 2020

[>] 2nd Winner of National Techno Art Web **Design Competition**

Bunda Mulia University • Apr 2019

- > 1st Winner of PNB Web Design Competition Bali State Polytechnic • Sep 2018
- ³ 2nd Winner of National Web design **Invention Competition** Udayana University • Jun 2018

A Languages

Indonesian

Native or bilingual proficiency

, English

Professional working proficiency